BYEONGJOO AHN

Porter Hall B5, 5000 Forbes Ave, Pittsburgh, PA 15213

Homepage: https://byeongjooahn.com > Email: bahn@cmu.edu

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research interests are in computational imaging and computer vision. I am interested in identifying visible hints offered by our physical surroundings such as interreflections, and developing imaging systems extending the visibility far beyond human ability such as the reconstruction of objects that are not in the direct line of sight or those with strong self-occlusions.

EDUCATION

Carnegie Mellon University

Pittsburgh, PA Sep. 2017 – Present

Ph.D. Candidate in Electrical and Computer Engineering

M.S. in Electrical Engineering and Computer Science

B.S. in Electrical and Computer Engineering

Advisors: Aswin C. Sankaranarayanan and Ioannis Gkioulekas

Seoul National University

Seoul, Korea

Mar. 2012 – Feb. 2014

Advisor: Kyoung Mu Lee

Thesis: "Occlusion-Aware Motion Deblurring for Bilayer Scenes"

Outstanding Thesis Award

Seoul National University

Seoul, Korea

Mar. 2008 – Feb. 2012

Summa Cum Laude

WORK EXPERIENCE

Carnegie Mellon University

Pittsburgh, PA

Research Assistant

Sep. 2017 – Present

- · Developed a full surround 3D imaging system of kaleidoscopic structured light, comprising a projector, a camera, and a kaleidoscope
- · Developed an imaging method to reconstruct hidden 3D shapes from multiply scattered photon using time-of-flight (ToF) information at picosecond timescale resolution (a.k.a. Non-Line-of-Sight Imaging)

Snap Inc. (Remote) New York, NY

Research Intern with Jian Wang and Shree Nayar, Computational Imaging Group

May. 2020 - Aug. 2020

· Worked on improving Snapcode/QR code detection by increasing the maximum scanning distance

Korea Institute of Science and Technology

Seoul, Korea

Research Scientist, Center for Imaging Media Research

Mar. 2014 - Aug. 2017

- · Developed multiple-camera capture system with 3D multi-view deblurring algorithm for dynamic 3D facial reconstruction
- · Developed polarized lighting system with an algorithm for real time acquisition of specular and diffuse normal maps from minimal number of polarized images
- · Developed web application for Korean food classification using Caffe and Flask web server

HP Labs
Palo Alto, CA

Research Intern with Irwin Sobel

Jan. 2012 - Feb. 2012

· Developed 3D video mobile controller using PTZ robot and Android phone

PUBLICATIONS

"Kaleidoscopic Structured Light"

Byeongjoo Ahn, Ioannis Gkioulekas, Aswin C. Sankaranarayanan *ACM Transactions on Graphics (Proc. SIGGRAPH ASIA)*, 2021

"Convolutional Approximations to the General Non-Line-of-Sight Imaging Operator"

Byeongjoo Ahn, Akshat Dave, Ashok Veeraraghavan, Ioannis Gkioulekas, Aswin C. Sankaranarayanan *IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV)*, 2019 (Oral Presentation)

"Occlusion-Aware Video Deblurring with a New Layered Blur Model"

Byeongjoo Ahn, Tae Hyun Kim, Wonsik Kim, Kyoung Mu Lee *arXiv preprint arXiv:1611.09572*, 2016

"Reduced Illumination Patterns for Acquisition of Specular and Diffuse Normal Maps"

Byeongjoo Ahn, Junghyun Cho, Taekyung Yoo, Ig-Jae Kim

ACM SIGGRAPH ASIA Poster, 2016

"Dynamic Scene Deblurring"

Tae Hyun Kim, Byeongjoo Ahn, Kyoung Mu Lee

IEEE International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV), 2013

AWARDS AND HONORS

Doctoral Study Abroad Scholarship, Korea Foundation for Advanced Studies	2017
Fulbright Graduate Study Award (Declined), Fulbright	2017
Best Poster Award, KIST R&D EXPO	2014
Outstanding Thesis Award, Department of EECS, Seoul National University	2014
Honorable Mention Award, Samsung Humantech Paper Award	2014
Graduate Scholarship, Kwanjeong Educational Foundation	2012
Presidential Science Scholarship, Korea Student Aid Foundation	2008

TEACHING

Teaching Assistant, Carnegie Mellon University

- · 15-463/663/862 Computational Photography
- · Recitation for 18-290 Signals and Systems

Fall 2020

Spring 2019, 2020

SERVICES

Reviewer, CVPR 2019-2022; ICCV 2019-2021; ECCV 2020; BMVC 2019; ICLR 2022

Student Volunteer, ACCV 2012; ICCP 2021

Volunteer, Camera Building Workshop as part of Gelfand Outreach Program at CMU (2019)

Mentor, CMU AI Mentoring Program (2021)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Proficient with MATLAB, Python, C/C++; Conversant with C#, JavaScript

GRADUATE COURSEWORK 15-868 Physics-based Rendering Spring 2021 33-353 **Intermediate Optics** Fall 2020 15-858 Discrete Differential Geometry Spring 2020 18-771 Linear Systems Fall 2019 10-707 Deep Learning Spring 2019 Convex Optimization 10-725 Fall 2018 Physics based Methods in Vision Spring 2018 16-823 Introduction to Machine Learning 10-701 Spring 2018 16-720B Computer Vision Fall 2017 18-793 Image and Video Processing Fall 2017 **Intermediate Statistics** 36-705 Fall 2017

Last updated: Dec 3, 2021